UNITE International Relations Department Records 6000/027
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE International Relations Department Records
1977-2001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE International Affairs Depratment
6000/027
28.5 cubic feet
28.5 linear ft.
Records.
This collection includes records of the International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU). Materials are unprocessed.
8239565
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 02, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 13, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/027 PUBS: UNITE International Relations Department Publications
Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Clothing trade--New York (State); Textile industry-- New York (State); Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. International Relations Department--Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees
8239565
- Women and Trade Unions, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Articles on American Labor American Union, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- International Women's Day, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Parental/Family Leave, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- U.S. Legislation, New and Pending, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Political Situation -- U.S., 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- U.S. Prison Labor, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- UNITE!, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- U.S. Garment and Textile Industries, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Garment & Textile Industries International, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Toycott/Icy Industries, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Used Clothing, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- US Aid. (Agency for Industrial Development), 1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- U.S. Economy, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- World Trade Organization (WTO), 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- World Bank and IMF, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- NGOs, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Clean Clothes Campaign, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Codes of Conduct, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Council of Economic Priorities (CEP), 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Apparel Industry Partnership Code of Conduct, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Monitoring Systems, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Sweatshops -- 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Sweatshops -- 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Global March Against Child Labor, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- UNITE!, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Child Labor U.S., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Child Labor, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- ORIT Child Labor Conference Santa Domingo - Nov. 6-8, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- General Articles of Interest, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Immigration and Migrant Workers, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Human Rights and Trade Unions, 1989-1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Factory Fires, 1995-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Footwear Industry, 1995-1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- 1997-1999 FITTVCC-ORI Payments (Box 3, Folder 8)
- ACC #01 - 10053 - 0 FITTVCC - ORI Bank Statements and Others, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- FITTVCC-ORI Bank Information and Dues Inf., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- FITTVCC-ORI All Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- FITTVCC-ORI 1998 American Express Documents (Box 3, Folder 12)
- ACC#01-13544-4 FITTVCC-ORI Bank Statements and Others, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- American Institute for Free Labor Development Field Personnel List, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Dues Analysis International FITTVCC/ORI, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- FITTVCC/ORI Copies of Deposit Slips, 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Bank Stop Payment and Others, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- FITTVCC/ORI Amalgamated Bank Information, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- FITTVCC/ORI Budget 1995, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- FITTVCC-ORI Audits Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- FITTVCC/ORI Budget and Others, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- FITTVCC/ORI, Affiliated List, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- FITTVCC-ORI Correspondence 1999 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- FITTVCC-ORI Correspondence and Others 1998 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- FITTVCC-ORI Congress Mexico, D.F. 1998 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- FITTVCC-ORI Photos Congress/98 Mexico D.F., 1998 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- FITTVCC/ORI Congress - Oct. 21 - 23, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- FITTVCC-ORI Exec. Bd. Meetings August/99, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- FITTVCC-ORI Dues, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- FITTVCC Money Wires, 1996-1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- FITTVCC International Corresp. 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- ITGLWF Montreal-Canada Oct'97 - Executive Committee Meet., 1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- FITTVCC-ORI, Newspapers and Bulletins, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Payments to Jose Ramirez FITTVCC/ORI Year 1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Record of Calls Jose Ramirez FITTVCC-ORI, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Relacion de Gastos de Las Giras Del Sec. Gral. A:, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Scope and Contents
  Spanish
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira Del Sec. General A Mexico D.F., 1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira Del Sec. General A: Honduras, Nicaragua, El Salvador y Guatemala, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira Del Sec. General A Washington D.C. (USA), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira Del Sec. General A Berlin (Alemania), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira Del Sec. General A R. Dominicana/Guatemala/CTR, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Relacion de Gastos. Gira Del Sec. Gral. A Brasil (Sao Paulo) Y Bolivia (LPAZ), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Relacion de Gastos, Gira Del Sec. Gral. A Florianapolis (Brasil), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Relacion de Gastos, Gira Del Sec. Gral. A Mexico D.F. Y Leon, Guanajuato, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Relacion de Gastos, Gira Del Sec. Gral. Honduras Y Nicaragua, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira Del Sec. Gral. Bruselas (Belgica), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira Del Sec. General A S.Domingo (Rep. Dominacana), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira Del Sec. General A Bruselas (Belgica), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira del Sec. General A Miami - USA, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira Del Sec. General A R.Janiero/ S.Paulo/ B.Aires, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- FITTVCC-ORI, Ramirez Travels Information, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- FITTVCC/ORI Women's Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Octubre, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Junio, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- FITTVCC/ORI 1998 Balances July - Dec. (Box 4, Folder 26)
- FITTVCC/ORI 1998 Balances January - April (Box 5, Folder 1)
- FITTVCC/ORI 1998 Balances May - August (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Women, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Folder (RATHER URGENT), 1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Maternity, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC), 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Global Economy, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- GSP, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Maquiladoras Plants, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- International Trade Central, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- NAFTA, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Multilateral Agreement on Investment (MAI), 1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Multinationals, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Trade and Workers Rights, 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Trade & Workers' Rights - Africa, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Child Labor, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- European Union, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Free Trade Zones, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- APEC, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Business for Social Responsibility (BSR), 1998 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Corporate Responsibility, 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- October 4, 1997 -- Day of Conscience (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Sweatshops -- 1995/1996 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Sweatshops -- 1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Sweatshops -- 1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Republic of Philippines, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Poland, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Portugal, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Singapore, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Spain, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Sri Lanka, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Swaziland, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Switzerland, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Taiwan, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Thailand, 1995-1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Sweden, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Turkey, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Uruguay, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Romania, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Russia, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Slovakia, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Uruguay, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Venezuela, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Vietnam, 1995-2000 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Yugoslavia/Bosnia, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Zairs/Congo, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Zimbabwe, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Zambia, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Ukraine, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- FITTVCC/ORI Correspondence 1999 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- FITTVCC Correspondence - 1997 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- FITTVCC, Correspondence 1996 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- FITTVCC/ORI Congress 1998 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- FITTVCC/ Presidium & Exec Comm Mtgs Costa Rica -- October 25-26, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- ITGLWF, News Latin America, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Documents, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira A: S.Paulo (Brasil) y B.Aires (Argentina), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira A: S. Domingo y San Salvador, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira A Copenhagen (Dinamarca), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- FITTVCC/ORI Travels Information 1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira A Guatemala, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira A Miami, Florida (U.S.A.), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances Sep-Dec. 1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances 1995 July-August (Box 7, Folder 10)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances Jan-April 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Mexico, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Morocco, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Nambia, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Nepal, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- New Zealand, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- The Netherlands, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Witness for Peace - Nicaragua, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Nicaragua, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Niger, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Nigeria, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Norway, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Palestine, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Panama, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Pakistan, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Papua New Guinea, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Paraguay, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Peru, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- ILO Tripartite Mtg on Labor Practices in Textile, Clothing, Leather & Footwear Industries -- Geneva, Oct. 16-20, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Petty Cash. Michelle Briones, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- UNITE Departmental Monthly Expense Report, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Expenses - Michele Briones 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Expenses -- 1999 Michele Briones (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Expenses -- 1998 Michele Briones (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Expenses - 1997 Michele Briones (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Expenses - Michele Briones 1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Expenses, Michele Briones 1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Mission Trips to Israel Jewish Labor Committee, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Macao, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- China: Textile/Apparel Industries, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- China Trade/Economy and Human Rights, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- China - Free Labor Movement, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- China, Dissidents, 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Zensen, Correspondence 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Zensen, Correspondence 2000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Zensen, Correspondence 1999 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Zensen, Correspondence 1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Zensen, Correspondence 1997 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Zensen Correspondence 1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Zensen Correspondence 1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- China -- Harry Wu, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Twarus General Correspondence, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- UNITE/Zensen Joint Conference October 2000 -- NYC & Washington (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Zensen/UNITE 9th Joint Conference Tokyo - April 22-24, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Takeshi Matsui (Zensen), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Committee for Free Cuba, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Czech Republic, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Denmark, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Dominica, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Dominican Republic - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Ecuador, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Egypt, 1997-2000 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- El Salvador - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- El Salvador 1995 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Eritrea, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Ethiopia, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Finland, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- France 2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- France 1999 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- France 1998 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- France 1997 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- France 1996 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- France 1995 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Federal Republic of Germany, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Fiji, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Gabon, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Grenada, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Guatemala, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Guatemala 1996/97, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- American Greetings, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Alfred Angelo, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Adidas/Chipman-Union, 1995-1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Augros, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Bardusch, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Barneys/Isetan, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Bogner, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Chentex, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Coleman, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Courtaulds, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Crown Textile, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Danaclon, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Domsey, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Eden Group, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Fruit of the Loom, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Freudenberg, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Fuji Film, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- The Gap, 1995-1999 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Gucci, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Guess, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  5 Photographs
- Kaolin, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Hoechst Celanese, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Koret, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Lear Corporation, 1995-1998 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Levi Strauss, 1995-1998 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Liz Claiborne, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- LVMH Group/Marc Jacobs, 1996-1999 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Maiden Form, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Mademoiselle Knitwear, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Mandarin International, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Mantex, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Narrow Fabrics of America/Hope Webbing, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- New Balance, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Nike (2), 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Nike (1), 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Peerless Clothing Co., 1995-1998 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- France, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- NAFTA, FYI Clippings, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Codes of Conduct, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- US/EU Symposing on Codes on Contact and Labor Standards, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- U.N. Social Summit, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- U.N. Commission on the Status of Women, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- U.N. Commission for Social Development, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Biographies, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- UNITE -- Merger, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Memos to UNITE Staff Miscellaneous, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- International Relations Dept. UNITE (Box 11, Folder 22)
- International Directors Meetings, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Memos From UNITE Staff Miscellaneous, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- UNITE General Executive Board, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- GEB International Relations Department Report 1997 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- UNITE Convention -- June 1999 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- SACTWU, 1996-1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Union-to-Union Programs South Africa 1996 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Union-to-Union Programs South Africa - 1995 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- ICFTU Online News on South Africa, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- South Africa General, 1996-2000 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Dominican Republic Organizing Project - 1996 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Dominican Republic Organizing Project 1995 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Honduras Organizing Project, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Honduras Organizing Project, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Guatemala Organizing Project, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Nicaragua Organizing Project, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- El Salvador Organizing Project, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Honduras Organizing Project 1996 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Otto Versand (GMBH & Co.), 1999 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Phillips Van Heusen (PVH), 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Reebok, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- River Falls, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Roberts, Cushman aka the Leather Factory, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Roots, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Safelite/Vistar/Belron/Plate Glass & Shatterproof Industries (PGASI)/ South African Breweries, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Sara Lee, 1994-2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Tenneco, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Sobel, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Texprint, Inc./Tokai Senko, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Thermopatch, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Total/Hutchinson, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- UCB, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- VF Corporation, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Warnaco (Hathaway & Lejaby), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- The Walt Disney Company, 1996-1999 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Wal-Mart, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- YKK Corp., 1988-1997 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Yu Hwa - Honduras, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Bonahan Apparel - Dominican Republic, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Zegna, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Costa Rica Organizing Project, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Central American Organizing Project, 1998-2000 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Visitors -- 2000 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Visitors -- 1999 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Visitors -- 1998 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Visitors 1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Visitors - 1996 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Visitors 1995 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Central American Delegation March 1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Hong Kong - Lee Cheuk Yan and Law Shin -- March 25, 1997 New York (Box 14, Folder 6)
- UNITE/FILTEA/FILTA/UILTA Meeting Italy -- September 10-11, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- FILTEA/FILTA/UILTA/UNITE Meeting New York, May 24-25, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Organizing Seminar -- Morocco July 3-14, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Jordan -- Laurie Kellogg June 1-5, 2000 H&S Seminar (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Jordan Seminar - Lynda Whittaker April 1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- ICEM World Conference for the Chemical and Pharmaceutical Industries, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- South Africa -- Richard Metcalf August 1997 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Cairo, Egypt - Michael Cavanaugh July 6-10, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Joint Meeting w/Italian Unions Venice, Italy -- September 1997 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Turkey - TEKSIF Seminar December 1996 -- Michele Briones (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Korea and the Philippines Keir Jorgensen - Nov. 1996 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Indonesia/ Hong Kong Clayola Brown - Sept 1996 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- ILO Tripartite Mtg on Globalization Geneva - 10/28-11/1/96 Joan Suarez, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Gemina/GFT seminar - Brussels October 16-17, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- ICFTU Circulars 1995 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- ITGLWF International Conference Copenhagen, 5-6 Oct. 1995 [Folder 1 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 1)
- ITGLWF International Conference Copenhagen, 5-6 Oct. 1995 [Folder 2 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 2)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Copenhagen ? Oct 1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Geneva 3-4 Nov 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Melbourne 13 April 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Melbourne 13 April 1996 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- China Human Rights, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Clippings 1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Japan, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Guatemala 1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Guyana, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Haiti, 1995-1999 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Honduras, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Hong Kong, 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Hungary, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Indonesia Muchtar Pakpahan, 1996-1998 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Indonesia 2000 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Indonesia 1999 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Indonesia 1998 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Indonesia 1997 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Indonesia 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Indonesia 1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Institute of Labour Management and Research, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- India, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Ireland, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Israel, 1995-2000 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Italy, 1996-2000 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Freedom House, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira A: Bruselas (Belgica), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira A: Santo Domingo (Republica Domincana), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira A: Guatema.Y Spsula (Honduras), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Relacion de Gastos de La gira A: San Salvador (El Salvador), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Relacion de Gastos/Gira Del Sec. Gral. Melbourne, Australia, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Relacion de Gastos/Gira Del Sec. Gral. Honduras y Guatemala, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Relacion de Gastos/ Gira Del Sec. Genral New York, U.S.A., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Relacion de Gastos/Gira Del Sec. Gral. Bogota, Colombia, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Relacion de Gastos/ Gira Del Sec. Gral. Goinia, Edo de Goias (Brasil), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Relacion de Gastos de La Gira Del Sec. Gral. A Lima, Peru, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Relacion de Gastos De La Gira Del. Sec. General A Honduras y C. Rica, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Relacion de Gastos - Gira Del Sec. General A Ginebra, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Relacion de Gastos - Gira Del Sec. General A S. Paulo, P.Alegre, Florianap. (Brasil), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- FITTVCC-ORI Balances Jan. Feb. March, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- FITTVCC-ORI Balances, April, May and June, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- FITTVCC-ORI Balances, July, August, Sep., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- FITTVCC-ORI Balances, Oct., Nov., December, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- FITTVCC-ORI Executive Committee Meeting, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- FITTVCC-ORI Exec. Bd. Meeting San Jose Costa Rica, Oct. 1996 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- FITTVCC-ORI, Exec. Bd. Meeting, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Women's Conference, March 96 Olga's Copies, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- FITTVCC-ORI, Women's Comm., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Women's! Committee Correspondence and Others, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- II Encuentro y Seminario Intern. De Mujeres Trabajadoras, FITTVCC, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Regional Asia, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Regional Latin America, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Regional Eastern Europe, 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Regional Europe, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Regional Central America, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Regional Middle East, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Regional Caribbean, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Memos to Jay Mazur, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Memos to Jay Mazur - 1996 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Memos from Jay Mazur, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous General Correspondence, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Memos to UNITE Staff -- Misc., 1997 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- U.S. Territories, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Regional Africa, 1997-2000 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Labor Issues and the International Financial Institutions 1996 Report to Congress (Box 17, Folder 17)
- African Growth and Opportunity Act, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- ITGLWF, Officers and Membership, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- ITGLWF, Affiliation Fees, 1999-2001 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- ETUC (European Trade Union Committee) -- 2000 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- ETUC: TCL Correspondence 1997-1999 (European Trade Union Comm: Textile, Clothing Leather) (Box 17, Folder 22)
- ITGLWF Euorpean Trade Union Committee (ETUC), 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 23)